<START:person>Joe<END> was the last person to see <START:person>Fred<END>. He saw him in <START:location>Boston<END> at McKenzie's pub at 3:00 where he paid $2.45 for an ale. <START:person>Joe<END> wanted to go to <START:location>Vermont<END> for the day to visit a cousin who works at <START:organization>IBM<END>, but <START:person>Sally<END> and he had to look for <START:person>Fred<END>.
